Truth. Honor. Loyalty. Family. What are you willing to sacrifice?
Pride and Glory is a crime, drama, mystery film directed by Gavin O'Connor.
A saga centered on a multi-generational family of New York City Police officers.
The family's moral codes are tested when Ray Tierney, investigates a case that reveals an
incendiary police corruption scandal involving his own brother-in-law.
For Ray, the truth is revelatory, a Pandora's Box that threatens to
upend not only the Tierney legacy but the entire NYPD.
Ray Tierney, played by Edward Norton.
Francis Tierney, Sr., played by Jon Voight.
Jimmy Eagan, played by Colin Farrell.
Francis Tierney, Jr., played by Noah Emmerich.
Abby Tierney, played by Jennifer Ehle.
Ruben Santiago, played by John Ortiz.
Pride and Glory is a 2008 American crime drama film directed by Gavin O'Connor, and
starring Edward Norton, Colin Farrell, Jon Voight and Noah Emmerich.
The film tells the story of a NYPD detective (Norton) who uncovers a police corruption scandal that implicates his
brother-in-law (Farrell), threatening to unravel their tightly bound family of law enforcement officers.
Pride and Glory was released in the United States on
October 24, 2008, by New Line Cinema.
It received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $43.4 million
worldwide against a production budget of $30 million.
The film explores themes of police, megacity, brother-in-law.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.